<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>The tech enthusiast on AXEL-CLERIS GAILLOTY</title><link>https://agailloty.github.io/fr/</link><description>Recent content in The tech enthusiast on AXEL-CLERIS GAILLOTY</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://agailloty.github.io/fr/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Installer WSL2 sur Linux</title><link>https://agailloty.github.io/fr/posts/wsl2-windows11/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://agailloty.github.io/fr/posts/wsl2-windows11/</guid><description>Le sous-système pour Linux Qu&amp;rsquo;est-ce ? Le sous système Linux pour Windows est une couche de compabilité développée par Microsoft qui permet faire fonctionner les binaires exécutables du système d&amp;rsquo;exploitation Linux de manière native sur Windows 10, 11 et Windows Server 2019 et ultérieur. La première version beta de WSL a été introduite en Août 2016 sur Windows 10. A cette époque seule Ubuntu (avec Bash par défaut) était supporté.</description></item><item><title>Le principe SOLID en C#</title><link>https://agailloty.github.io/fr/posts/solid-principles/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://agailloty.github.io/fr/posts/solid-principles/</guid><description/></item><item><title>The revolution will be complete when the language is perfect</title><link>https://agailloty.github.io/fr/posts/language-perfect/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://agailloty.github.io/fr/posts/language-perfect/</guid><description>He moved over to the window Since about that time, war had been literally continuous, though strictly speaking it had not always been the same war. For several months during his childhood there had been confused street fighting in London itself, some of which he remembered vividly.
Inside the flat a fruity voice was reading out a list of figures which had something to do with the production of pig iron.</description></item><item><title>Sanity is not statistical</title><link>https://agailloty.github.io/fr/posts/sanity-not-statistical/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://agailloty.github.io/fr/posts/sanity-not-statistical/</guid><description>There was no way of knowing whose version would finally be adopted Once again he glanced at his rival in the opposite cubicle. Something seemed to tell him with certainty that Tillotson was busy on the same job as himself. There was no way of knowing whose version would finally be adopted, but he felt a profound conviction that it would be his own
Mare torrentur Mare torrentur tenuerunt Iovemque crudelis erat non manuque nullaque Pyreneus, evocet pectus, nube.</description></item><item><title>It's a beautiful thing, the destruction of words</title><link>https://agailloty.github.io/fr/posts/destruction-of-words/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://agailloty.github.io/fr/posts/destruction-of-words/</guid><description>He moved over to the window Lorem markdownum comes; pro est modo famulus, quo quod neu manibus aether his nomine, Aurora, voce. Ipse virga res vidit profanis vocatos, quod vestigia cineres, dum silva in vapor. Tendite caelestibus quam, sub inplet prole eveniet superi rus proles venenis potestas Tereo pluribus sunto.
Perque cessisse, hoc tum auras sinuosa. Pressant nec vinci primoque quoque funibus est: et tempore vetitorum? Coercet tantum adsensibus religata protinus venturas et Achilli, nat iam cum deque.</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://agailloty.github.io/fr/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://agailloty.github.io/fr/about/</guid><description>Je m&amp;rsquo;appelle Axel. Je vis dans ce beau pays qu&amp;rsquo;on appelle la France. Je suis diplômé d&amp;rsquo;un Master en économie appliquée avec une dominante en économétrie et statistique. Je suis en général intéressé par la résolution de problèmes. Ce que j&amp;rsquo;aime le plus, c&amp;rsquo;est l&amp;rsquo;heuristique dans la résolution de problèmes.
Qu&amp;rsquo;il s&amp;rsquo;agisse de problèmes économiques tels que la théorie des jeux ou de défis de codage, j&amp;rsquo;adore quand je suis poussé à mes limites.</description></item></channel></rss>